本字幕由YYeTs字幕组原创翻译
www.ZiMuZu.tv 欢迎交流
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
饥饿
的青春
第二季  第四集
翻译  冰蓝  aaaBao   roaddog
校对  roaddog
后期  斯人   总监  roaddog
时间轴  aaaBao
对不起  我现在就煮咖啡
Oh, sorry. I'll make some more coffee right now.
没事  我来
No worries. I'll do it.
因为你不想让我肮脏的农民手碰吗
'Cause you don't want my grubby peasant hands on it?
不是  傻瓜
No, silly billy.
我可以自己来
I can do it myself.
我还在床上做梦  我上班要迟到了
Okay, I'm still in bed dreaming, and I'm gonna be late for work.
艾略特  你心情很好
Elliot, you're in a pretty good mood,
明天就是你40岁生日了
considering your big 4-0 is tomorrow.
我还以为你会惊慌失措呢
I thought you might be freaking out.
更像是十分激动
More like getting my freak on.
和安德烈一起
With Andre.
这是我第一次生日时有男朋友
This is the first time I've ever had a boyfriend on my birthday.
39年的悲伤
39 years of sorrow,
我终于可以穿着生日礼服
and I finally get to celebrate my birthday
庆祝生日了
in my birthday suit.
天啊  我真喜欢有男朋友的艾略特
Oh my god, I love Elliot with a boyfriend.
他开心时我也开心
When he's happy, I'm happy.
也许我们还会成为朋友  那就太棒了
Maybe we'll even be friends, which would be great,
因为人不会告诉朋友
because friends don't tell friends
她看起来像廉价商店的妓女
they look like dime store hookers.
朋友会说  你穿这条裙子好漂亮
Friends say, "Hey, you look cute in that dress."
裙子真漂亮
Hey, cute dress.
好了  我们得让这辆爱情火车继续开
Okay, that's it. We've got to keep this love train going.
我要给安德烈打电话
I'm calling Andre.
艾略特会拥有最浪漫的生日晚餐
Elliot's about to have the most romantic birthday dinner ever.
那主意很棒
That's a pretty good idea.
真可惜  那比不过我的礼物
Too bad it's not gonna top my present.
因为我赚的钱最多
Because I make the most money here,
还被顶尖杂志称为创意天才
and I was called a creative genius by a top publication.
是《每月吹嘘》吗
Oh, was it Bragging Monthly?
怎么  你想看是什么礼物吗  好我去拿
What's that? You want to see what it is? Okay, I'll get it.
我找安德烈花店的安德烈
Hi, can I speak to Andre of Flowers by Andre?
你好  安德烈  我是加比
Hey, Andre, it's Gabi.
是的  烦人的金发厨师
Yes, the annoying blonde cook.
艾略特要过40岁生日了  我想给他个惊喜
Listen, I'm surprising Elliot for his 40th birthday
做一顿浪漫晚餐  显然也想请你做他的约会对象
with a romantic dinner, and obviously I want you to be his date.
好  看看日程然后打给我
Okay, great. Check your schedule, get back to me.
怎么了
What?
天啊
Oh my god.
艾略特和安德烈  好有爱
Elliot and Andre. That's so cute.
这肯定让你觉得自己的礼物很烂
I bet this makes you feel pretty lousy about your gift.
天啊
Oh my god!
安德烈刚发现我今年40而不是32岁
Andre just found out I'm turning 40 instead of 32
跟我分手了
and broke up with me.
什么
What?
这真是最烂的生日
This is officially the worst birthday ever!
天啊
Oh my god!
别担心  艾略特
Don't worry, Elliot.
-安德烈不会是你最后一个约会对象  -是啊
- Andre's not the last guy you'll ever date. - Yeah.
你肯定会被很多男人甩掉的
I'm sure you'll get dumped by tons of guys.
我这辈子只爱过三个人
I've only ever loved three men in my life.
安德烈  大学里暗恋的埃兰
Andre, my college crush Alan,
还有骚当
and Adam Levine.
我知道这听起来很疯狂
And I know it sounds crazy,
但安德烈是唯一一个也爱我的人
but Andre's the only one who loved me back.
我知道这可能不是提的最佳时机
I know this might not be the best time to bring this up,
但《连线》的人明天要来拍我的桌面了
but the guys from Wired are coming to photograph my desk tomorrow
要发表在"成功之桌"专栏上
for the Desk For Success column.
我们准备好了吗
Are we ready?
-没有  -那么
- No. - So...
我这话是很友好的
And I mean this in the nicest possible way,
你觉得什么时候能好啊
when do you think we'll be ready?
等有人再爱上我怎么样
How about when someone loves me again?
所以是永远不会
So never!
早上好  亲爱的们
Good morning, beautiful people!
我说这是个很棒的早上
I said what a good morning it is.
安德烈和艾略特分手了  因为他40岁了
Andre broke up with Elliot because he's turning 40.
那么多原因  他只选了这个吗
Out of all the reasons, that's what he picked?
真遗憾  亲爱的
Oh, I'm sorry, baby.
你想听听别人的痛苦的故事吗
You want to hear a story about somebody else's pain?
那总是能让你开心
That always cheers you up.
我前夫科尔曼
My ex-husband Coleman,
为了一个更年轻的女人甩了我
who dumped me for a younger woman,
刚被一个更年轻的女人甩了
just got dumped by a younger woman...
在结婚典礼上
at the altar.
至少他俩结婚了
At least he got to the altar.
安德烈是怎么知道我真实年龄的
How did Andre find out my real age anyway?
只有你们三个人知道
The only people who knew were you three.
哪一个告诉的他
Which one of you told him?
不是我
Not me.
我还以为你50呢
I thought you were 50.
对不起  是我
I am so sorry. It was me.
天啊  是你
Oh my god, it was you!
艾略特  我真的很抱歉
Listen, Elliot, I'm really sorry.
我只是想为你做点好事
I was just trying to do something nice for you.
那本来是个惊喜的  我们要成为朋友的
It was gonna be a surprise. We were gonna be friends.
你毁了那一切  对吧
Well, you ruined that, didn't you?
我永远也不会原谅你  加比·戴蒙德
I will never forgive you, Gabi Diamond!
他只是需要一点时间
He just needs some time.
永远不会
Never!
你还好吗
How you doin'?
我的人生结束了
My life's over.
你不明白
You don't understand.
基佬年里  40岁等于是80岁
40 is 80 in gay years.
拜托  我不明白吗
Please. I don't understand?
跟我一样大的男人想要20岁的女人
Men my age want women in their 20s.
这意味着我只能拥有120岁的男人
Which means the only man I can get is 120.
真好  我跟你一样又胖又老了
Great. I'm in the same fat, old boat as you.
没错
That's right.
你知道当我觉得自己老时怎么做吗
You know what I do when I'm feeling old?
我涂上睫毛膏  打理头发
I get my lashes done, I freshen up the weave,
买新唇膏
I buy new lipstick--
我是基佬  但没那么基
I'm gay, but not that gay.
我刚有了个主意
Oh, I just got an idea.
你知道我前夫科尔曼
You know my ex Coleman
是城里最棒的整形医生
is the top plastic surgeon in the city.
你觉得我需要整形吗
You think I need plastic surgery?
整一下我能像32的
I could pass for 32.
整一下我还能像霉霉呢
And I could pass for Taylor Swift.
来看看
Let's see.
这里
Over here...
我好美
I'm beautiful.
好了
Okay.
我这就去给科尔曼打电话
I'm gonna call Coleman right now.
好  等等  别打
Yes. Wait, no.
你不能为了我去跟那劈腿男打交道
I can't make you deal with that cheater for me.
别说傻话了
Oh, that's ridiculous.
我带你去
I'll take you myself.
-我希望你开心  -从什么时候开始
- I want you to be happy. - Since when?
因为是你的生日
Since it's your birthday.
因为科尔曼被甩了  你想当面嘲笑他吧
And since Coleman got dumped, you want to rub it in his face?
贱男不就是该被这么教训吗
Isn't that how you teach a dog a lesson?
我觉得我有办法...
Okay, I think I've figured out a way...
来帮我吗
To help me?
上个月  《连线》 拍了伊隆·马斯克的飘浮桌
Last month, Wired featured Elon Musk at his hover-desk.
特斯拉汽车首席执行官
是的  我看到了  好酷的
Oh yeah! I saw that. That was really cool!
我帮不上忙  对吗
I'm not helping, am I?
我知道这对你来说或许算不上什么大事
Look, I know this might not seem like a big deal to you,
但我这行的所有人都会看这个专栏
But everybody in my business reads this column.
风险投资家  潜在客户  软件开发者
Venture capitalists, potential clients, software developers--
所以你想看起来酷一点吗
So you want to seem cool?
-没错  -别担心  好吗
- Yes! - Don't worry, okay?
他会在你接受拍摄前调整好情绪的
You're gonna have him back in time for your shoot.
我想出了最能表达
I figured out the perfect
"抱歉  我毁了你的生日"的礼物
"I'm sorry I ruined your birthday" present.
他爸妈知道他40了  对吗
His parents know he's 40, right?
-怎么会不知道  -我是这么计划的
- Why wouldn't they? - So here's my plan.
因为艾略特少有机会见他的父母
Since Elliot rarely gets a chance to see his parents,
所以我想请他们一家吃一顿丰盛的韩式晚餐
I'm inviting them to a five-course Korean dinner.
他会喜欢的
He'll love that.
-现在就给他们打电话  -好的
- Here, let's call them now. - Okay.
喂  帕克先生吗  我是加比·戴蒙德
Hi, Mr. Park? It's Gabi Diamond.
艾略特的同事
I work with Elliot.
对  那个讨人厌的金发厨师
Yes, the annoying blonde cook.
艾略特的男友跟他分手了
Anyway, Elliot's boyfriend broke up with him
我不希望他孤单一人过生日
and I don't want him to be alone on his big day,
所以我想问问你们是否愿意飞过来
so I was wondering if maybe you could fly in
明晚和他一起吃生日晚餐
for a birthday dinner tomorrow night.
太好了  问一下帕克夫人  给我回电
Okay, great. Check with Mrs. Park. Call me back.
你打算请他们在哪吃晚餐
So, where are you planning on having this dinner?
我以为你不会问呢  你家阳台
I thought you'd never ask. Your terrace.
没问题  晚餐费用我出
No problem. And I want to pay for the dinner.
但你已经出了他们的机票钱了
Oh, but you're already paying for their flights.
天呐
Oh my God!
刚刚有人代我向我爸妈出柜了
Someone just outed me to my parents!
等等
Wait.
你爸妈不知道你是基佬吗
Your parents didn't know you were gay?
不知道  他们超级传统的
No. They're super traditional.
甚至都不怎么过性生活
They don't even like sex with each other.
-他们是怎么知道的  -加比干的
- How the hell did they find out? - Gabi did it.
我需要他  他是我的"桌语者"
I need him. He's the desk whisperer.
知道吗  乔什
You know what, Josh?
我想到了最好的生日礼物
I just thought of the perfect birthday gift.
让那个小婊砸从我眼前消失
Tell that dime store hooker to get out of my face.
-好吧  我能...  -加比  请回家
- Okay, can I-- - Gabi, home.
再见
Bye.
说你裙子可爱  我是骗你的
And that cute dress? I lied!
你回来的真早
You're home early.
你做了什么
What'd you do?
我导致了艾略特的男友跟他分手
I caused Elliot's boyfriend to break up with him,
然后还向他爸妈出柜了
and then I outed him to his parents,
要是我再这么说下去  听起来一切都不错
and if I keep talking like this, everything sounds great!
我勒个去
Holy crap.
对了  我有没有提到明天是他的生日
Oh yeah. And did I mention it's his birthday tomorrow?
等等  乔什炒你鱿鱼了吗
Wait. So, Josh fired you?
没  索菲亚  乔什没解雇我
No, Sofia, Josh didn't fire me.
只是我们都觉得
We just have a mutual agreement
我不在他家会好些
that things are better when I'm not around.
我该怎么弥补
How do I fix this?
你毁了他的恋情
Okay, well, you destroyed his relationship,
告诉了他爸妈他是基佬
you told his parents he was gay.
你有时间做饭吗
When do you find time to cook?
我知道了  我给艾略特找个新男友就行了
Hey, I know. I'll just find Elliot a new boyfriend.
他说他这一生只爱过三个男人
He said he's only loved three men in his entire life.
安德烈  骚当
Andre, Adam Levine,
还有个名叫埃兰的大学同学
and some guy named Alan from college.
太好了  我们去找大学同学埃兰吧
That's great. So we find Alan from college.
我刚要说这句话
I was gonna say that!
你不让我说完  我永远学不聪明
If you don't let me get there, I'm never gonna learn.
好了  开工
Okay, all right.
-我打开了艾略特的脸书主页  -好的
- I'm on Elliot's Facebook page. - Okay.
只有两个人叫埃兰
There's only two Alans.
埃兰·锡克和埃兰·洛文斯汀
Alan Thicke and Alan Lowenstein.
前一个埃兰是加拿大演员  生于1947年
我知道了  是埃兰·洛文斯汀
I know. It's Alan Lowenstein
因为他是伯克利毕业的
because he went to Berkeley
艾略特也是这所学校毕业的
and that is also where Elliot went to college.
是啊  只有这个原因了
Yes, that's the only reason we know which Alan.
今天正式是你的生日了
Well, today is officially your birthday.
生日快乐  看见没
Happy birthday. See?
我把安德烈的脸改成了我的
It's my face instead of Andre's.
这代表了我们的友情
It represents our friendship--
老板  公关
Boss, publicist.
互帮互助
Always there for each other.
别说了  我决定不庆祝我的生日
Stop. I've decided not to celebrate my birthday.
我明白了  好兄弟
I get it, big guy.
你想专心在《连线》的拍照上
You want to focus on the photo shoot with Wired.
乔什  在整容咨询结束后
Josh, I'm gonna be able to focus better
我会更好地专心的
after my cosmetic surgery consultation.
什么
What?
艾略特  你不需要整容
Elliot, you don't need plastic surgery.
让詹姆斯医生决定吧
We'll let Dr. James decide that.
尤兰达的前夫吗
Yolanda's ex-husband?
是的  她替我预约的
Yes, she got me an appointment.
正要带我去呢
She's taking me right now.
她想见他是因为她听说他现在单身
She wants to see him because she heard he's single.
不  她不喜欢他
No, she doesn't like him.
只是想当面嘲笑他被甩
She just wants to rub the breakup in his face.
我不觉得她这打扮是想要当面嘲笑他
I don't think that's what she wants to rub in his face.
-能走了吗  -我知道是怎么一回事了
- You ready? - Look, I see what's going on here.
你利用艾略特作为见科尔曼的借口
You're using Elliot as an excuse to see Coleman.
拜托  看看他这张松弛的脸
Oh, please. Look at his saggy face.
他看起来就像一条等人解救的巴哥犬
He looks like a rescue pug.
这样谁会救他啊
That's never gonna get rescued.
尤兰达
Yolanda.
你辛勤工作多年
You worked day and night for years
供科尔曼读医学院
to put Coleman through medical school.
他一当上医生
The minute he became a doctor,
就跟他的助手私奔了
he ran off with his assistant.
现在是报应的时候了
And now it is payback time.
他单身  又脆弱
He is single and vulnerable.
我要施展魅力
I am gonna turn on the charm,
让他约我出去
and get him to take me out,
等把他玩弄于鼓掌之中以后
and right when I got him wrapped around my finger,
再狠狠甩了他  就像他当初一样
I'm gonna dump his sorry ass like he dumped mine.
不敢相信能找到你  埃兰  艾略特一定很高兴
I can't believe I found you, Alan. Elliot's gonna be so excited.
你觉得高兴的是他吗
You think he's gonna be excited.
我在专业定向会上就对他有好感了
I've had a crush on him since freshman orientation.
老实说  我就是那样给自己"定向"的
In fact, that's the way I discovered my orientation.
你真有趣
That's funny. You're funny.
"有趣"吗  人不帅才会这么说吧
Funny? That's what people say when someone's not cute.
天啊  我紧张的要汗流浃背了
Oh god, I'm so nervous I'm schvitzing up a storm.
我不知道那词什么意思
I don't know what schvitzing is,
但我觉得你没有
but I can't tell you're doing it.
别担心  没事的
Don't worry. You're gonna be fine.
-你还单着  多棒呀  -是啊
- How lucky is it that you're single? - Yeah.
就像中彩票一样棒
I'm like a lotto winner.
不敢相信艾略特还是单身
I can't believe Elliot's still single.
他那么抢手
He's such a catch.
艾略特·帕克吗
Elliot... Park?
真希望你能提前几周通知我
You know, I wish you would've given me a few weeks' notice.
我好减几斤肥
I would've lost five pounds.
我骗谁呢
Eh, who am I kidding?
我懂的  你想给他个惊喜
Oh, I get it. You want to surprise him.
终于做件对的事惊喜他吧
Surprise him by doing something right.
稍等
Wait here.
加比
Gabi.
艾略特回来不能发现你在这
Elliot cannot come home and find you here.
他不在真好  听着  我有其它办法了
Oh good. He's gone. Listen, I have another plan.
我觉得你还不懂"计划"这词
I think you're using the word "plan" wrong.
这回不会错  好了  有请...
This one's a winner. Okay, meet...
埃兰·洛文斯汀  艾略特久违的大学爱人
Alan Lowenstein, Elliot's long lost college love.
知道他的真实年龄  他的性向
He knows his real age, knows he's gay,
还一直是单身
and he's still single.
你干嘛总提这茬
Why do you keep saying that?
你也不对任何药物过敏吗
And you're not allergic to any medications?
如果有  我也不在乎
If I am, I don't care.
麻晕我  撕下这张老皮
Dope me up, peel this off,
换个新脸上去
and slap a new face on me.
我觉得该进来跟科尔曼打声招呼
Just thought I'd poke my head in and say a quick hey to Coleman.
尤兰达  你没说你会来啊
Yolanda, you didn't tell me you were coming.
快  去检查下我保时捷的车胎
Quick, go check the tires on my Porsche.
不  真的  去看看
No, seriously, go check.
看看你
Wow, look at you.
如果我不知道
If I didn't know better,
还以为你也动过刀子了呢
I would think you went to one of my competitors.
-别闹  -对  闭嘴
- Oh, stop. - Yeah, stop.
因为如果你觉得她好看  我走人
Because if you think she looks good, I'm out of here.
抱歉  我就是被她
Sorry. I just got a little distracted
那双大"眼睛"
by those big beautiful...
分了神
eyes.
你的确很喜欢我的"眼睛"
You always did get lost in my... eyes.
我们都懂  你在说她的奶子
We get it. You're talking about her boobies.
真是易如反掌
It's like taking candy from a baby.
艾略特  我觉得首先要
So, Elliot, I think the first thing to do
给你的脸微整一下
is a subtle facelift.
不要"微整"
The hell with subtle.
我要你把我皮拉到像高空跳伞那么紧
I want to get pulled so tight I look like I'm sky-diving.
你怎么样  尤尤
So, how you been, Yo-yo?
挺好的  科科
Oh, can't complain, Co-co.
听说你分手了真抱歉
I was so sorry to hear about your breakup.
等尤尤和科科调完情
If Yo-yo and Co-co are done flirting,
艾艾想整成韩版的马特·达蒙
El-el wants to look like the Korean Matt Damon.
真希望你是我今天最后一个病人了
I wish I didn't have another patient after this.
为什么  我要动那么多吗
Why? Do I need that much work?
我今晚想请你吃晚餐
I'd like to take you to dinner tonight.
-没问题  -真棒
- That would be fine. - Excellent.
会很有趣的
This is gonna be fun.
你绝对想不到
Oh, you have no idea.
我有个主意
Hey, here's an idea.
别拍她马屁了  赶快整整我屁股
Quit kissing her ass and start lifting mine.
是门卫打来的
Okay, that was the doorman.
艾略特在上楼了
Elliot's on his way up right now.
我看起来如何
How do I look?
解开一个  两个还是三个扣子好
One button unbuttoned? Or two? Or three?
我又不是亚瑟小子  还是一个吧
Who am I? Usher? I'll do one.
你看起来很可爱  埃兰·洛文斯汀
You look adorable, Alan Lowenstein.
现在你乖乖坐着  我去走廊找他
Now you sit right there, and I'm gonna go meet him in the hall.
好
Okay.
我过生日可没请你
I did not invite you to my birthday.
但你结婚会请我的哦
But you will invite me to your wedding.
我有个生日惊喜给你
I have a birthday surprise for you.
你这次又干什么了  杀了我的猫吗
What'd you do this time, kill my cat?
不  还记得你大学暗恋的埃兰吗
No. Do you remember your college crush Alan?
-他来了  -什么
- Well, he's here. - What?
没错  小寿星
Yeah, you heard me, birthday boy.
他现在就坐在屋里
He's sitting on the other side of that door right now,
很高兴地想见你
and he's so excited to see you.
真的吗
Seriously?
-真的吗  -真的
- Seriously? - Yeah.
你怎么找到埃兰·奥夏的
How did you find Alan O'Shay?
奥夏吗
O'Shay?
我擦
Oh, ----.
加比  让开  我要见埃兰
Gabi, move! I want to see Alan.
不行
No.
你可不想太猴急
You don't want to seem too eager.
但那是我的招牌动作啊
But that's my signature move.
如果你的新招牌动作
What if your new signature move
是姗姗来迟呢
is being fashionably late?
怎么样  再见  在这等着哦
Ooh, what about that? Okay, bye. Wait here!
他来了吗
Is he here?
还没
Uh, not quite yet.
坏消息  埃兰  艾略特病了
Bad news, Alan. Elliot's sick.
你要是传染上可不好
And I would hate for you to get it.
是啊  我很容易生病的
Well, I don't want it. I am very susceptible.
没错  我也是这么想的
Yeah, uh-huh. That's what I thought.
我们从这走  从那走  走
Let's go this way. Go that way, go that way.
艾略特·帕克
Elliot Park?
埃兰·洛文斯汀
Alan Lowenstein?
-真惊喜  -是啊
- Surprise. - Yes.
真是惊喜
What a surprise.
好吧  怎么回事
All right. What's happening here?
感觉像回到我是希伯莱语学校里唯一没被
It feels like when I was the only boy in Hebrew school
邀请去珍妮·施耐德成人礼的男生一样
not invited to Jenny Schneider's bat mitzvah.
管她呢  反正那贱人也肥成猪了
Whatever. Bitch got fat.
埃兰  我犯了个大错
Listen, Alan, I made a horrible mistake.
你不是那个埃兰
You're the wrong Alan.
她以为你是埃兰·奥夏
She thought you were Alan O'Shay.
埃兰·奥夏吗
Alan O'Shay?
我倒是想
Oh, I wish.
看来你们都喜欢同一个埃兰嘛
Hey, looks like you both love the same Alan.
不如你们边享用我
Why don't you talk about him
给你们准备的丰盛大餐  边聊聊他吧
over the magnificent dinner that I made you?
所以我都不该来这的
So, I'm not even supposed to be here.
真是丢脸
This is so embarrassing.
-我该走了  -别走
- I should go. - No, don't.
这是她办砸的事  她该走
She's the one who screwed this up. She should go.
你留下
You stay.
否则我等下也会泡在浴缸里暴食那桌菜的
Otherwise I'm just gonna shame-eat all this in the bathtub later.
艾略特·帕克泡在浴缸里
Elliot Park in the bathtub?
谁给我跟冰棒降降温
Oy, I need a popsicle.
真是绅士
Oh, such a gentleman.
你不用一直送我回乔什家的
You didn't have to walk me all the way back to Josh's.
但我很高兴你送了
But I'm glad you did.
我想告诉艾略特我可以挤出个
I wanted to tell Elliot I could squeeze him in
下周的手术时间给他
for surgery appointment next week.
只是因为这个吗
That's the only reason?
不
No.
我在拥有的时候从来不懂珍惜
I never knew what I had when I had it.
现在懂了  我很怀念
Now that I do, I miss it.
你在说我  是吗
You're talking about me, right?
当然
Damn right.
所以...
So?
埃兰和艾略特怎么样
How are Alan and Elliot doing?
我只能说这是我开的第二瓶酒了
Let's just say I'm opening another bottle of wine.
那进展不错咯
So it's going well.
我不知道  是我自己喝的
I have no idea. This is for me.
幸福小俩口回来了
There's the happy couple.
幸福过分了吧
Almost too happy.
看  艾略特在那呢
Look, there's Elliot.
不如你去告诉他手术日程的好消息吧
Why don't you go tell him the good news about your schedule.
看到他表情没  乔什
You see his face, Josh?
你是说跟你一样的傻笑吗
You mean that same stupid grin I see on yours?
我搞得定  亲爱的  一切尽在掌握
Oh, I got this. It's all part of an act, baby.
等一下  他会送我去电梯
Next up, he's gonna walk me to the elevator.
我会给他毕生难忘的一个吻
I'm gonna give him the kiss of a lifetime.
然后说  "等等  科尔曼
Then I'm gonna say, "Hold up, Coleman.
我有话跟你说
I have something to say to you.
报应是个叫尤兰达的婊子"
Payback's a bitch named Yolanda!"
你要先测个血型
You'll just need to get your bloodwork done,
不过下周肯定可以了
but you should be all set for next week.
谢谢你帮我排进去
Thanks for squeezing me in.
还有给我亲友折扣
And thanks for the friends and family discount.
等等  我没说有...
Wait. We didn't say anything about--
再见
Bye!
-怎么了  -我不想说
- What? - I don't want to say anything.
但还是要说
But I will.
不敢相信你要去整容
I can't believe you're getting plastic surgery.
干嘛要乱动自己完美的脸呢
Why do you want to mess with perfection?
就像那些做无麸百吉饼的人一样
It's like those people who make the gluten-free bagels.
什么
What?
你的脸那么帅  那么年轻
Your face is so handsome and youthful.
那两条浓眉
Those thick luscious eyebrows.
就像两只美丽的毛毛虫
They're like two magnificent caterpillars
在说着"我才不要当蝴蝶"
who said, "To hell with becoming butterflies."
如果我不知道我们一样大
If I didn't know we were the same age,
我只敢相信你最多32
I'd swear you weren't a day over 32.
知道吗
You know,
加比今晚请你来
Gabi inviting you here tonight
或许是她犯过最好的错了
might have been the best mistake she's ever made.
敬错误
To mistakes.
尤兰达
Yolanda...
今晚真的很棒
today was amazing.
就像以前一样
Just like old times.
比以前更好  是你请客的
Better. You paid.
知道吗  如果按不到电梯钮
You know, if I don't push that button,
我可走不掉
I will never leave.
那你按啊
So push it.
等等
Hold it.
科尔曼  我有话跟你说
Coleman, I have something to say to you.
说什么
What's that?
你周五晚上有空吗
Are you free friday night?
我知道今天不能再糟
I know this day was a disaster,
但每个人过生日都该有蛋糕吃
but everybody deserves a cake on their birthday.
这是分层草莓松饼
It's a tiered strawberry shortcake
配塔希提香草奶油和鲜莓
with Tahitian-vanilla whipped cream and fresh berries.
他会很期待把它扔你脸上的
Ooh, he is gonna love throwing that in your face.
那我还是等下再点蜡烛吧
I'll hold off on lighting the candles.
怎么样
So?
报复成功了吗
Did you get your revenge?
杀得他片甲不留
Oh, I made out like a bandit.
艾略特  不像你的人生
Elliot, unlike your life,
你的蛋糕可没被我搞砸
your cake is one thing I'd never screw up.
-唱  -等等
- Sing-- - Hold on.
我要先说句话
I'd like to say something first.
-这个生日很糟  -是我  我干的
- This birthday has sucked. - That was me. I did that.
但还有一件好事
There's been one bright spot
就是又和埃兰见面了
and that's been reconnecting with Alan.
是我  我干的
That was me. I did that.
这位可爱  风趣  英俊的男人
This sweet, funny, adorable man
让我知道我不需要整容
made me realize I don't need plastic surgery.
我觉得40岁会是我最好的年华
I think 40 could be my best year yet.
等等  我都42了  你怎么会40
Wait. How can you be 40 if I'm 42?
怎么样
How's it going?
他说这次是自己拍过最精彩的照片
He says it's going to be one of the best ones yet.
一个还在白纸上记录自己
The tech guy who still writes out his ideas
创意的程序员
on butcher block paper.
我可不是一般帅  我是复古小开
I'm not just cool. I'm retro cool.
谢谢你  艾略特
Thank you, Elliot.
也谢谢你过去几天为我做了那么多
Thank you for putting up with me the last few days.
都搞定了
All done here.
我能说我超爱这幅画吗
Can I just say I love the painting?
现在我知道该送我丈夫什么生日礼物了
Now I know what to get my husband for his birthday.
我很高兴我们终于做了次
I'm so thrilled we're finally doing
成功同志的桌面拍照
a gay desk for success.
至少我爸妈会高兴我嫁了个百万富翁
Well, at least my parents will be happy I married a millionaire.
先生
Sir?